Welcome to the night, the car is laid out for show
Star shine is so bright, watch the secret sun fall
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds
we are king
spicy shirt slip
hey what's up what's up guys hey hi thank you sorry let me play a little music you liked it
you liked it okay hi hi guys shit oh my god look at my hair the fuck sorry oh gosh
yeah i kind of hangled up
Like I don't know if there's like one there's like a big break in that
Weird okay
Hi, how are you? Uh, hey, hello, Ivy. How are you everybody? I'm in a good mood today. Um, so
How are you? Okay, so I have an announcement about the CLAP program. If you are interested,
and I'm going to probably write a song about it, too. It'll explain it better, but this is like
basically, this is the new thing, just further notice. There you go. You see it,
pretty straightforward, and that's gonna be the final.
Okay, hopefully, we have some fun with that, okay?
So today is third iThursday, so let's see.
We'll have a good panel today.
Yeah, I woke up, you know, I just joined TikTok,
and
No, I'd like to eventually hey piranha. What's up? I bet you like start streaming on that. I think I need like a thousand followers, though
psyche awakens on tiktok
I'll try to get a link for you guys
I'll do some other stuff
They need to try that or Pittsburgh. Oh, they are at the convention. Hold on. Give me my glasses
Shit
Okay. Hold on.
They're at the convention.
Yeah, go over to Benny and Trident. Yeah, there's Benny and Trident.
Last year, this time last year, I was...
I think I spent all weekend. Like, pretty much they streamed all weekend. I was there the whole time.
Yeah, you like these? Yeah, these are my readers.
I just need these to see the type.
It's like, I'm gonna get another pair too, because I really like...
Oops, I love having a...
Glasses and I'm gonna get the Jeffrey Dahmer the Jeff Jeffrey Dahmer kind of things. Oh, that's a new it's a new hum big thing
Yeah
Really? Yeah
So, yes, I'm getting a
Your favorite on a man over there
But uh, yeah, I uh
Some everyone was like you're squinting like like mr. McGoo you need to maybe um put on some
readers and so
Yeah, I'm getting the dog. I'm getting the Dahmer aviator style next
okay, so
Getting a little bit of assistance
With the script with the scripting the show and maybe formatting a little bit better
Like I'm gonna start I'm incorporating more readings. Like, you know, I'll do readings on the energy of panel
I'll do I'll do just your readings about people's relationship
but if they you know and different kinds of stuff like people that come on the show more incorporated also do like a
A general energy reading of like the the whole like cat at the beginning of the show
I'll do like a collective at the end. I will maybe if you through I'll do free readings for people as well as
The paid readings
The banner up in a second, but yeah, so there's gonna be a lot of ways to
Yeah, you like the chaos one. Yeah, you like the school. There you go
Okay, let me skip. There you go. Okay. Okay, so it says, okay, let me say it. Okay.
So it says, good evening, witches, watchers, and wild things. Welcome back to Psyche Awakens,
the only panel where the cars hit harder than your ex and the trolls hit send with one brain cell left.
I'm your host Psyche and tonight we're going full chaos live hero open panel deep insight perhaps at least one person saying something absolutely unhinged
Local in so let's start with the collective reading. This is for anyone
Watching live. We're in the future take what resonates leave the rest and if it drags you maybe it's meant to okay
Let's see
They're born right now, okay
So, let's see, what's the energy in the room right now?
Here's the energy in the room.
The energy in the room today.
The energy in this cat, the panel, the me, everybody.
What's the energy in the room today?
How's the energy looking?
It's kind of message for the day.
Okay.
Okay, KMT cups.
King of cups energy this is like some this is some very emotionally matured
energy this is like a little bit if he's also a doorway right remember this is
like little she doesn't eat me drink me this is a this is a doorway you can quite
get the key in right king of cups the king of cups you know
Traditionally, he, you know, he, he might have a few drinks, but he can control his alcohol, though.
And, yeah, it says the king of teacups represents a kind, caring, paternal figure.
He tries his very best to help when his guidance is sought.
If you're feeling overwhelmed by a challenge or conundrum, the king of teacups suggests that you seek out
wise advice of someone with experience in these matters and your best interests at heart.
Well, I kind of feel like I resonate with that.
And I hope you guys, too, I know a lot of you
are big helpers and supporters of people.
So what are we not seeing?
What are we not seeing today?
What are we not seeing?
What are we missing something?
Let's try to make it self-known.
Okay.
Ooh, okay, we're not seeing the seven of swords.
Okay, well, this is the seven of swords, you know, traditionally the thief card
And so, you know, maybe there's somebody that is you know in the background in the shadows like in a pocket watching or
Which bad intentions? I don't know it says seven of spears represents deception and trickery
Someone may be trying to confuse or hoodwink you pay close attention to your intuition now trust your gut feelings
If a situation feels off to you now, it probably is okay. You're even like little feelings, right?
Hey, there's some things to look out for here.
This person does not, doesn't sound like, right?
They're saying weird things, right?
Well, just these little, like little nudges, right?
So the third is what spirits wants to scream at us right now.
So what does spirit wants to scream at us right now?
Spirit wants to really get the message
about something right now, okay?
Hopefully this message will resonate with the ones
it's supposed to resonate with, okay?
There you go
There you go. Okay. Oh
Night of Cups one. Oh, it came out with two
Okay
Ace of Cups and the night of Cups, okay
Maybe this night of cups is coming with this ace of cups. It's kind of love offer or something
I don't know. There's something there's an umbrella and a tea cup
Does that mean anything to you or maybe like it almost seems like that's pouring, you know
And maybe there's maybe like, you know, get out your umbrella at night
Be pouring some emotion some rain or something like that water always represents emotions. Let's see the ace of cups
The ace of cups is like, you know, you'd be getting in love or like some kind of new relationship that can grow into something more
The ace of cups says the ace of cups represents new friendships relationships and personal connections meet new people with an open mind
And an open heart because someone specials meant to come into your life
Whether they're outgoing as the mad hatter or dependable as the dodo this person's gonna end up being an important connection for you
Okay, that's it's another one came out the night if teacups came out, too
That's someone bringing you like the love offer like the nights. I'll always
Doing the special delivery, right? It says the night of tea cups is the charming person with dramatic flair known for a chivalry
He's the first to open the door for you or shield you from the passing or pouring room with an umbrella
The tarot card advising you to get in touch with your emotional creativity
And a love letter write a song or redecorate in a way that inspires you
Okay
So maybe there's a new a new beginning with this with this a charming person with some dramatic flair
I don't know if you know this person, but no
And that's that's a dodo. Is that the dodo right? That is the dodo. All right, dodo umbrella
Okay, we'll convict a child of make CRM XX9
Plug me somewhere prove it. Okay
Okay, but yeah, welcome to all the kick people. I'm so far just gotten a bunch of advertising kick, but I
do appreciate
Hey, wait, I think there's like, you know when they put a blindfold around you and
And say they're gonna stab you in the heart or something. Okay
Let's see
Okay, so I
Not qualified for this. Okay, so what is J?
J
There's J in the room. Oh
Help I need somebody
Not just anybody. Okay, let's see. Let's be a word of advice. Let's do a word of advice card
I feel final words advice word advice. What's what's the advice for the chat? What we look for to?
Be aware of the energy. Maybe we're supposed to carry some. Yeah, what's the advice for us? Come on
And that's shimmy zero okay, I'm sure me at least one person here. Well, what did I get okay?
Okay
Three of flowers, okay, that's number three, okay, I
Like this is like, you know three threes oftentimes will be like a third party
And so I'd say I always think of like somebody getting involved that you know trying you later
But can be just you know in a better way can be just working together in a good way
It says three of flowers reminds you that importance of teamwork cooperation and good communication
You can't accomplish everything by yourself ask for the support to bring your creative vision and help you your plans reach the full potential
So even though they're going in different directions are all on the same kind of page, right?
Okay, so
There you go, that is a cool card, that is a cool card.
So I'll do some more readings.
Guys, I have, for members, if you'd like a reading,
you get priority for free readings
and readings with extra cards.
You can go ahead and just drop the member emoji.
It's the crystal ball.
So I have for dinner.
I have not eaten yet, I'm thinking,
I'm gonna order maybe, I don't know,
order something a little bit.
I got a couple of drinks.
Yeah.
So hopefully everyone's doing great. I love you. You know, it's like a
Yeah, I think I'm a privilege, you know, you guys, you know, you guys are
There's a lot of options
But you say you like me and you come here really video
warms the old part, right so
Hopefully all
Be able to have a great night with you guys. So
This is one of the favorite drinks those pineapple coconut. Good
Little bit strong
But I'm really happy guys. Oh, I guess my neighbors brought me all this liquor. They brought me
Let's see. There's a bottle of Casa Doris. There's a bottle of Irish cream
There's a bottle of Jamison and some kind of other tequila. I think there's a couple bottles of tequila
Yeah, I think it's from October from their wedding or something
I'm not a big
Hard alcohol person. I'm just gonna probably mix it with some stuff
Yeah, cheers cheers guys Lulu IV so and okay, and guys we're also I think
Seven I think we're at 93 members and so seven away from the hundred I can have 13 emojis
But under 100 once I did 200 I can I'll have be able to have things I think probably maybe 20
I'll get some other cool stuff there.
I'll make it so you guys have a big selection of emojis
to talk from, I'll put some messages and stuff.
Hey, Tracy, good to see you.
Oh, Tracy, I love you, I haven't seen you for a while.
Good to see you, thanks for being here.
Yeah, so yeah, the emojis are super cool though.
I mean, I'm gonna work on some of them that aren't.
It's good. I mean, it's like I'm getting better at it. I'm doing a lot of graphics too. You can see the graphics. Hey BSB be good to see ya
Yeah, but it's really you know, it's a reach and also guys there's over a hundred
So there's some of them are like eight hours long. You know, there's like a lot of there's hours and hours and hours of stuff
And just the members
Also, we'll do more cards for you. Of course, I'll do free readings for everybody that wants one and
And, you know, upgraded readings if you'd like or if you'd like to send a donation, I'll put the banner up with that information.
And we're all good. Okay, so that's that. And then I'll put this. Make sure you also like, share, subscribe. I really appreciate that.
It's been a little bit slower lately, but, you know, it's always quality over quantity. Yeah, there we go. Like, subscribe.
I wish I could move that around a little bit.
I'll read my name a little bit.
But hi, everybody.
Yeah, we're having a great little group already,
22 people in chat.
So, guys, you know, my community board,
I think I opened it up for everybody to post there.
Okay, I think as long as you're a subscriber,
you can post on the community board if you'd like to,
you know.
I would say, you know, if you want to share your own site,
just share your own, make sure you share your own,
and share it like one time, you know?
Or, you know, one time, maybe a month or something, right?
Maybe active, but, you know, just let's keep it,
to kind of spam free.
Let's see, happy birthday to extruding the sun.
Okay, yeah, we got cancer, cancer, season, still?
Yes, Jen, what's up?
How are you, Jen?
Yes, I'm sorry
Yes
Will you add women's tanks or women's t-shirts sure I mean yeah, oh so you're talking about the shopping, okay?
So yeah, I'm going to I was just kind of testing out. I'm also in another website called another t-shirt website
and I'm gonna
Think I might have women's on that. It just has to wait for a little bit first populate the store
Yeah, women's tank tops and women's t-shirts. I got you. I got you on that. Yes. I can make those
and if you'd like
Specific ideas for shirts to you guys. I mean I have some logos. I have my cat logo. It's really cool. It's this one
It's just gonna be on this is the
My new logo I made it's really I think gonna be good-looking right to be nice yellow on black
kind of really cool. I like that a lot. So, oh, thank you, Jan. Awesome. Yeah, and so yeah,
it's pretty cool. I have the shop, I mean, the Shopify or something like that.
Or we're here with Teespring. I think, yes, Teespring. And I set that up and
we'll see if we can get some other products too. It's pretty cool. Also, I'll try to get some
My some of my decks. I'll try to get my this way some links up for those one with the vampire teeth and that one with the
Onscreen that a cat on screen. Yeah, okay. I'll do the vampire teeth, too
Yeah, that'd be cool
Yeah, I'm gonna do a fish taco shirt, too. I'm gonna do a really funny fish taco shirt. I'm still happy
I'm trying to figure out the funniest joke joke for it, but
Oh, you like that. Yeah, that's the beautiful
Yes
You got it guys, you know, it's no no problem because those are they're printed on demand
There's shirts and so I'm pretty much design everything we offer every style they have available. So
Okay
Thank you guys
I don't really appreciate that and you guys are just super stars
And thank you also, I know I've gotten
getting some really nice super chats and stuff.
What's up, Ellie?
It's good to see you.
Really nice guys, you know.
I know, I do appreciate everything I've got also.
Amazon list, thank you so much for everybody
that's gotten some decks of cards and.
Hey, there's Trixie.
Hey Trix, wanna say hi?
And I'm also, yeah, I've got some cards coming too on T-Mail.
Aw, yeah, that'd be so cool.
I'd love to see it when you get it, when you get it.
To put a picture.
May you blow me?
Maybe.
Oh, you like it, Tracy?
Okay, thank you.
Yeah, you notice I've been putting a little bit
of more effort into keeping it professional,
keeping it fun, keeping it.
Looking good and getting better. I want to keep improving. Yes
So
Yeah, we've had some interesting panels lately, you know, you try it out
Yeah, this is basically the little cutie Lola was around
I'm sorry
Sorry
Yeah, that's what I mean. Yeah, it's the worst. Um, you know, not having your cat. I'm sorry
But thank you and you guys also if you do have suggestions, you know, I
Am you know, I do have times to experiment with different ideas and stuff on the show. And so if you have a
Great idea you'd like to share, you know
Proposition or anything I'm also going to add my add an email address to
my
My description right, but it is psyche tarot channel at gmail.com
So if you do want to reach out or maybe a personal reading or you know, just with me any kind of comment or
Letter or any anything you can think of you want to keep
Contact me with go ahead. Oh
She was oh, she's got it 18. That's like, you know, that's I get scared because Rudy's kind of old
I think he's like maybe I don't know if he's I heard he was 15 at first
She's like it's 15 years old then I heard she's 16 then I heard he might be 17 and so it's like oh my gosh, this is like
It's not they don't live long enough. I wish I could live like a long time Rudy's really adorable
It's getting kind of old
so
So let's start it out
But yeah guys, it's finally finally finally got my like my kitchen my dishes are done my all my laundry is done
I just need to fold it up still
and
My tables cleaned off my cards are all organized my books are organized
My couch is put together everything's more comfortable
Just feel like I'm able to finally get a breath breath in life, right? It's just like, okay
What's up fish talk? What's up? Memphis shay? What's up girl? This yeah
Yeah, well fish tacos do sound good. But yeah, now it appears close
Those rubios if I get anything but once you eat fish tacos from up here rubios tastes like
Kaka ex-boyfriends. Oh, I'm sorry that the cat was mean growing up
But he said it for some reason the cat was nice to you. Oh that cats will pick favorites. I've heard that a lot
but you know
We won't have a boyfriend
That would
Very much help right now, but and I very much appreciate it. I don't know anything
Fish tacos. Yeah, I might order some
Definitely would if I you see I find where they have them
Let's see
Actually, they have they just have some good secret rush. They love the Tony's at the pier. Yeah, that's what I
Tony's is really good fish. I think I might have that
Me check
Rub hub you might fall
That sounds really good actually, okay, I think they have a I think they're about ten bucks
Doot-doot-do
We have let's welcome our friend
What's up? Okay. You're good. Okay. What's up, dude? How are you?
What was that you cut out? Oh
How are you doing? I'm doing pretty good. Just got back from Hong Kong. Oh
Oh, yeah, you're the guy from China, right? Yeah
Okay, how is that? How is that?
Yeah, it turns out the Chinese people don't really like Scientology, so we had
shit, you know
I thought that might be a problem, you know, aren't they have like a don't they have like a national religion or something?
1399 fish tacos. I think that's a good deal. Yeah, I think most of them are Buddhist
Buddhist. Yeah, and the what was interesting about the the Chinese Buddhism though is like, you know
When they went in took over Tibet, right? Yeah, they uh, you know, they deposed the deposed the Dalai Lama
So they post they have their own version of the llama and it's like basically
Promoting the you know, it promotes, you know, the the national
Party right and so it's a little bit of a different kind of Buddhism
I would say the normal booze and it's a little bit kind of like if our government was to start a religion
It kind of looks like that. We have also another guest. Let me just make sure this is the right person. Hello. Hello, sir
Alpha
Yo, Rob
You're here. Okay. Everyone's here. We're all good. Okay. There we go
Alpha Damien's here
Okay, what am I gonna have this dish tacos?
where's Joe at? Joe who? I'm not really sure. Joe Shipley? The white guy? Yeah, the ginger.
Okay, the ginger guy. Yeah, I'm not sure. I haven't seen him today. Probably will stop
by. You like Joe? Yeah, you received Joe and I kiss? No, I haven't.
You have it?
Yeah, Joe actually came, and he came to visit me.
And here, we had a little, let me show you.
I have it on video.
I have a little, you know, it was captured forever in time.
OK, so this is, like, you know, he came out to see me.
Yeah, I'll put it on the full screen.
Dang, I didn't know Joe swung that way
Oh, I think you're muted
Yeah, that one. Yeah, you like to hear like turn. What's up? Yeah, so that was Joe and I
Can't say yeah, it was a magical trip
Joe's a silly guy. Yeah, I like him. I love I love redheads. They're so temperamental and and funny
They are they are they got that only on psychies 100% right?
It is weird. Nobody thought it was weird. You see how skinny I am. I am skinny
Kim look at this
Hey everybody, so I'm sorry. I'll take it off this. There we go. So we're here with Rick and Alfa Damian. What's up guys?
Cheers
What you drinking?
It's a Smirnoff ice pineapple coconut smash. It's a tasty
8% alcohol
Yep
So I've been sleeping like I've been
basically awake all night and then
sleep all day and
So hey, it's gotty here. What's up, Gotti wasted away in Margarita. Yeah
Yeah, I'm gonna get some tacos tonight, I guess because
Tacos are some of my favorite things
I've actually almost turned into a fish taco. Hey, what's up Gotti? How many of those you got?
I got one of they got one of those and then I got a
Which this one's a pineapple
I just need I just need to see any of the couple last night. I drank and I hardly even I didn't finish it
I didn't finish one. Yo, yo, Gotti
Thank you. Go on a racer. Okay, that's not very nice this day. I mean, it's okay. Yes, it's true
I do I could it basically, you know, you get a job in one of those movies, right? But
It's not very nice
Okay, where's the fish tacos here? Mm-hmm
It's just was looking at them oh fish taco game down fish tacos, and what else do I want? I think maybe just those
Fish tacos and how about
Yeah, sake this pods pretty lame tonight. Was everybody at?
I know it was just started, you know, I started like 41 minutes ago. Wow. Where's everybody? It is 30 people in the chat everybody
Come on guys everyone
Shout out something you want a reading like let's let's have some fun. No, I'm gonna break out the speedos yet
Good
I'm sorry. We should like Gotti on the show. I mean, he's allowed on the show. He's welcome up anytime
Where's actually
Where's page?
Paging page. Oh, where's the link? The link should be pinned. I didn't get it. What the hell?
We're snorky yet. There's the link a lecture might come up here. Come on up lecture
There we go
There you go guys, okay, so I'm gonna get these fish tacos then
That's a little oh, excuse me. Excuse me
A little treat.
Oh, let me see if I can get up.
Oh, we're in a little bit.
Okay, so there's the link, I'll pin the link.
Come on guys, pin the link.
The link's not there?
It's not?
Oh, shit.
Oh, here comes the lecturer.
Welcome. Hey, hey, what's up? How are you? What's up? I'm good. How are you doing?
Good, sweetie. Like you're at your top. Yeah, thank you. Lecture's hot. I love animal print.
Are you doing? It's so hot today. Oh my god.
It is. My background is backwards. Interesting. Uh-oh. It says,
Oh, but it says 22 and you can see that.
Like that's backwards.
Did you notice it in backwards?
Look, OK.
Oh, it's forward for me.
It's just to pay that for you, I guess.
Yeah, it's past 22.
Oh, OK.
It looks great, DJ.
It looks really good.
That's like my dream studio.
If I could have my dream studio.
But in real life, it's not quite this cool.
But I do have some sparkle lights and some cool posters.
And yeah.
Not cool though. I got a new computer chair and stuff. That was awesome
Gotta have a good chair
Yeah, good chair and I got some new dance moves
Want to see them? Yeah, definitely. Can we do any music?
Sure hold on a second. I
Keep those music. Let me see. Well, I need a dance on here. Oh, here's a dance on it's the disco. Let me see it goes
Oh, hold on. That's perfect. Hmm. Let me see this work. Hold on
Your dance of this
You
Yeah, working
curtain swaying mods holding the line with psyche at the helm everything's fine we've dodged a few
bombs in the chat room nights still made it through because you're gang of style yeah i love it
is this a song about you it is
Oh, and the cats!
Yep.
Got him!
Whoa!
Oh yeah, I got belly dancing moves too.
oh my frozen right now yep oh so free freezes if i try to put new ones in there
pretty cool song who made this song yep who made it for you i made it you made it awesome yeah
i made a bunch good job
Thank you
Okay, it's almost over in psyche's world. Oh, welcome in this song
Oh, it's beautiful. Yeah, yeah, yeah
There we go
Who is the roof? Yeah, there we go. She got some moves. They're good. Do you think Star Wars galacy dance moves? Yeah, thank you, Tracy. Yeah. Well, you know, lecture really was a big, you know, influence and what, you know, because I started out with doing like, you know, I got to try all the canva and that like, and I had canva before when I had my other business. Yeah, it's like so hot. Oh, oh yeah, that was awesome. Yeah.
So I got Canva, and then I started like using the chat GPT and like chat GPT is like really been really helpful like
Didn't I tell you like yeah, I mean I've used I used it a few years ago like it's like it really like
Like now you can put down your link like your any show you have any show it will analyze the show
It'll go through. I mean, it's like before dinner. It really wasn't able to do that
It also remembers has a memory now or remember memory, but it's not perfect like
Make all my images 16 by 9 aspect ratio, and it still fucks it up
Yeah, I found it I found it to be very helpful which one you like
It's it's called character.ai
Okay, okay. Yeah, so what is it you but you can like you can you can use these premade characters
So it's like what was it?
Cool pre-made characters like little avatars. Well, they're so yeah, there's something that will even take your photo make it
Make an avatar of you and yeah, that's how I made your
Cartoon psyche. Oh, yeah. Oh
Uh-huh. Oh, yeah, those are so cool. I mean
I'll just talk to you and get some advice about some software and stuff because call me any time we can go over it and
Because I've been doing it for a couple years now like at least a full year
Plus doing
Images the videos. I'm not as good at but I just made one recently. Do you guys want to see it?
Sure. Well, they changed the little icons in here. Mm-hmm a little bit different format different layout
Well, I've been looking for like, you know, I've been trying to put some
Some video to the AI song, but that's like I haven't found like a free service yet. We can put it on here
I think this is funny nobody else thinks it's funny
That's my co-host on the show
Larry oh
My gosh they changed StreamYard, and it's worse than it ever was
I
Not that bad for me, but I try to share a video now
It doesn't even say share video you have to know what the icon means if you hover over it
It doesn't say what it is doesn't have that stuff so you can X out of it easily
Oops, what what do you say? I'm gonna miss it. Hi, Jamie's cat boys
Hey, Jamie. How are you sweetie? Forget it? Oh?
No, okay. Tell me go ahead and tell me I want to hear. Oh, no, no, no, it's okay
I would like to hear please that ship is so
Okay, he said you fuses now, okay, I just have bad hearing sometimes so many loud concerts and
So I did want to hear what you said. I just didn't hear OMG. What concerts so many
Totally a Facebook a Facebook was read. I know we would use it and it was true. Yeah, it wasn't free. Yeah, no one's gonna pay for
The going paid for X, you know, which one I like is Gemini
Google's AI and it does a lot of images for free more than chat GPT does
Yeah chat GBT cuts you off at like what five images a day or something. Yeah, I mean, yeah
I will do like 20
The Gemini is so hard with like it won't do any any big any people, you know, it's like won't you perfect
Like you came with people. Oh, it does. Okay. Well, it wasn't when I was busy, but yeah, maybe oh, I put a picture in
Oh, yeah, you just save a picture and then the little plus sign at the bottom you can put it push that
Upload a picture and just say make this random dude into a cartoon and it will do it
Oh, that's cool. I mean a is kind of stupid still
Yeah, I mean, it's like I think the AI is like it's like talking to it in a very
Technical way is like it's an excellent that's what I do. I'm saying it a very good. It's like a very
Yeah, you do. You do have to talk to it in a technical way almost. You have to talk like a computer. That's why my co-host Casey is so good at it, because he's just like robotic basically.
Yeah, he's like emotions. What are those? I am a robot. He's just like that. And so he's super good at talking to this AI. Me, not so much. I'm like, make it look like it's feeling happy.
They really your your your voice sounds really your life last time's really fake. Oh, who's that laughing?
It sounded very fake
Damian was that alpha Damian? I hate it. Hey to fake laugh. Yeah, that's not to be real
Nothing, you just had a fake laugh meet Rick. I like your picture with that
Statue
Thank you. That's when I was in DC. I took that I like that. Thank you
Yeah, I actually fought in a war
You did. Which war? Which one?
Here. Let me think. It has to be Afghanistan.
Yeah, you know, I don't really think it was a war. It was just they
shit me off to Afghanistan. Troop 125. Okay.
What's the tune?
It's a tune 47.
Okay, well, okay, hopefully you're telling the truth because you don't have to fight in a war to be a soldier
You're still a soldier. It doesn't matter if it's wartime or not. You still serve the country. So thank you
Yeah, I didn't really fight I was more on I like I don't really like using weapons
Okay, but he has a role that's important that
Why'd you in the military if you're not into weapons? So I mean it seems like it's like that's kind of what it's about
I don't know
My daddy told me I had to
Okay, okay. Well, he put
You know in some countries like Israel everybody has to go into the military for a certain amount of time after they graduate
What they consider high school?
And I kind of agree with that
Yeah, well, that's basically there's almost like the drafts here, you know, it would be
Conscript conscription and that's also you know, but it's totally different from the draft
It's even in non wartime. They they all have to go do a military service, right? I know the Mormons have to do a
mission
so everybody has to go into the military and serve and I think it's good discipline and for
Integrity, you know showing up when you say you're gonna show up and have people's backs that you say you're gonna have their backs
You know, I think those are important lessons to learn and some people don't learn them if they don't go into the military
They just are out there
They see what their family does or what their friends do and they're out there selling drugs and doing all this bullshit
You know, and I think that the military could be good for a lot of those people
Right track instead of on the wrong track. Sometimes it is end of selling drugs and weapons in the military
I mean it is a good place for like black
It could help some people too
Sure sure sure I mean it's a good for discipline. It's good for you know breaking down the individual ego and like you know
Putting into like a hive mind, which is good for of course, you know for for a million
Any kind of team organization right just was to have like the the one man see that's great that your son is in the Marines
I love that. Yeah, thank him for yeah, whatever great
What's up, my my cousin was in the Air Force. He went on a scholarship for water polo to the Air Force Academy in Colorado
Yeah, and but then he couldn't serve or he couldn't fly because he had a heart murmur that they didn't even know about
But when he did his physical there in the Air Force, they found his heart murmur
Found out he had to have like a procedure to correct it. He had a faulty heart
But he still didn't get to fly
But he got to be one of their special forces
He's retired now. He's out now
He he got out like yeah
Untrackable says the military saved his life
Yeah, DJ you make my heart murmur
She's she's a nurse that she can take it. She can take it. He's EKG of you, too. You know, yeah
Now you're being
How are you doing EKG psyche? Oh, it is okay. Yeah, you got to take their shirt off and put electrodes on their chest
Have you ever done that give you then call the Colostomies or the the colonics or the what is not colonic via?
I applied for a job once, I went into the job and did the interview and then they took me into the procedure room where they had some dude butt up, ass up, with a scope in his ass and the picture of his colon on the screen and I was like, I don't
Like never mind for me. Yeah, and never mind. Yeah, they offered me the job. They really wanted me. I was just like
I don't know. You see every day Harry. You've seen worse. I've seen worse. I've seen way worse
Depends on the guy's athlete, but you know, it's like it is
It is, you know, the waxers do it for pennies on the dollar of a nurse, you know, so it's, you know, it's really, you know, waxers make really good money, like comparable to nurses, some of the nurses that do like the injections to for Botox or I never got into that.
I was still trying to help, I was working in pediatrics, so I was still trying to help children, like get well and handle their lot in life because I was sick as a child, so I know what it's like.
But waxers do make pretty good money.
I mean, not bad.
I mean, it depends on where they work.
If they work in a nail salon, not going to make as much as if they work in an actual waxing boutique.
Do waxers make good money or like nurses don't make enough?
I think they should pay nurses more personally.
I feel like, yeah, nurses can make, I had to look at my social security like the other day
and I made almost 100 grand one year.
Oh, wow.
But I was working, this was back in the early 2000s too.
So, but I was working a lot of overtime.
and they should still pay nurses more
because of the shit that we go through
and the shit that we wade through on a daily basis.
I know, I've heard some stories,
I've heard some terrible stories from you and other nurses.
We have a lot of nurses here actually.
We have a, I think it's one of the largest pop-ups.
Who was on last night?
Is that Joe?
Spongebob?
No, that's a intracable.
Hi, intracable.
Yeah, Spongebob is an MD, I think, isn't she?
She's a doctor, yeah, she's a physician, she said.
That's great.
I did a show last week and she was with me like the whole five hours that I did this show. She was there the whole time. She was so awesome.
I love her. She's sweet. She's great
And it's so sweet. Yeah, I was yeah, we also
Go ahead
No, I'm gonna say Christine as well. Christine's the nurse and uh, you know
Tiger Butterfly is the nurse and who else?
Yeah, we've been uh, yeah a bunch of nurses almost. I'm sorry. You didn't mean to interrupt go ahead
Oh
He's a he's a nurse too. He's a hospice or a retirement home or something
Yeah, I love my fellow nurses. What up nurses shout out
You make the world go around and
Good doctors too. It's buggy. I'm sure she's an amazing doctor. Yeah, listen to you might just learn some
Yeah, I think last night. Maybe she was getting some shit talked
I was working so I didn't have the audio on but I just saw some of the you know
I had the captions on I was like what these people better not be talking shit on my girl spunky summer
If they do it again, I will come up there and fucking rip them a new one
You're on track. Yeah, are you doing man?
He's muted. Oh, there we go. Hi intracable
Yeah, I'm doing good. I
Just heard a snippet
I'm not exactly sure what you guys were getting into
but um
Did you hear that you wanted to comment on?
Something about like the military can be good for some people
Yeah
You know, they just maybe it took me back and
You know not everything is what you see on TV. Were you in the military? Yes
And there are there's a thousand jobs you can pick from not everybody is a kick-ass
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
Um, you know, you got finance you got cooks you got medics you you have supply you have
And there's there's even different jobs are important to make the military run
That's all it can contribute. They contribute the same the same as people that were fighting. You know, it's all it's the whole organization
right I heard a story not too long ago and this is like a
It's like a funny piece of history. It's like, why should you fear the United States military? It's because
Within 24 hours, there will be a Burger King in enemy territory and that means and that means we have secured
The spot, you know what I'm saying that means our base is here and it's permanent
That that and you know, you know something like that that brings morale to the troops
Whereas you hear like some of these other places that are going on right now
No, they're snatching people up off the streets and you lose a million people in three years
Like
I think he's talking about a different country now. Okay. Okay. What country are you talking about?
Where's a million people in a year who lost a million people in a year?
Russia. Oh
Okay, well, but they started that war
Yeah, hello
Well, I I'm not sure I you don't you can't quote me on the numbers
But I don't think we lost 30 to 40,000 in 20 years
But even one is too many to lose. I don't even like losing one person to war. It's just so
Oh, yeah, everybody matters, but you know when you get to
I don't think they've lost a million people in Russia
Yeah, I mean that's a huge amount of people that that's almost like a but you know the Holocaust to like they you know there was
You know what 11 million people then and then there was a holodomor in Russia in like the 40s the 30s and 40s
That was like the famine there was like almost like 15 million people maybe or you know a huge amount of people
And so you know we are the losses we experienced are very
Small compared to some of the past some of the past wars, but you know
Who knows what would happen if there's another world war, right?
Well, if you use the right war tactics and you use drones as much as possible instead
of, you know, human aircrafts, then...
It can reduce the amount of people lost and I think right, but that's called duty that at that point though
It's called duty. It's like why do you think they put those games out for young kids these days, right?
It's random to kill but that's the fact that thing is like if you're killing by pushing a button
It's like kind of like you know because they even did test with like people when it's like like a
We called the men that's scared ghosts and they'll say like the military people where they can world war two
They did testing and that's like they would intentionally
Miss they would like they would like this. It is not intense. It's not even intentional. It was like subconsciously
There's an aversion. There's an aversion to hit like, you know killing somebody like that
And so they would always war video games out these days is because they get our kids at a young age
To learn to play war
They they just like what was that?
Ready Player One, that movie, I think it was called Ready Player One.
Anyways, they have these kids ready to do these war scenarios
and they're a little bit desensitized to it, or a lot desensitized, it depends.
And, um...
I I really do think that a lot of these video games are training our children well
Absolutely, that's what they are programming. It's like everything else movies movies music. It's all programming versus
It can be tough because
Like if anybody's ever heard of the rules of war
It's like if you want to if you want to take something
Why sit here and waste so many lives just blow it up on day one
There will be no questions asked
That's against the rules of war
Exactly. What what are the rules?
Civilians would die. We agreed that we would fight for it
But then you wind up sending a whole bunch of your youth to die and then they want to complain about
Population and all this bullshit. Hey, if you want it if you want that land that bad
Kill everybody there kill everybody
Because it's not a game. It's war
War isn't it's like oh my god these nations they agree to not those nuclear weapons
Children kill women and children to take the land you're saying that that's appropriate
Yeah, that's not appropriate
Women and children children's not appropriate. It's war
Well, a handshake deal, it means they couldn't work things out, it means they couldn't get
their commerce to get together, it means somebody wanted something and somebody wanted to defend
something and it all turned out to be bullshit when if you really wanted it that bad, why
even play by the fucking rules?
Well, because they made rules to prevent deaths of innocent people.
Yeah, but they really don't care about innocent people, they're not innocent, according to them they're not innocent people.
They still do kill innocent people, you're right, women and children, it still happens, but they try to prevent it as much as they can.
But you know I did my own kind of, it was my own study, so when I was working as a nurse I would have to sedate people a lot for procedures, painful procedures.
So put them under sedation was almost under anesthesia, but just not quite under anesthesia
But as a nurse I can still put them that deep under sedation and I found that these gamers
You couldn't sedate them very well
Because they I don't know why I can't explain it to you, but
Throughout my career the gamers would not take sedation. Well, they would not be sedated
It was like you could not put them to sleep
They just needed more and more drugs and more drugs and they were still wide awake and anxious or whatever
but
from my it wasn't a very scientific study. It was just like a general study, but
think that video games do have an effect on our children and they do affect pain
management tolerate tolerate how much they tolerate pain and it's it's something
I think people should actually study and do a real also the oh desensitizing also
I mean but yeah they've been it's been a big thing about the violence and video
games how it contributes to violence in society how it did and then nobody was
saying oh yeah the world we don't teach you how to shoot in video games well you
It's like soon war will be like that where you don't have to actually shoot a gun you're just you're just be pushing a button
It'll be firing something or dropping something and so so you don't need to know how to shoot
Yeah, it's a kill right and I told my son he couldn't have video games until he was 12
I thought 12 was a pretty good age because his friends were playing him at like eight and nine
He would still go to their house and play these games, right?
By the way, because I can't control other people's houses.
So but at 12, I said, OK, let's get you these video games.
They weren't the most violent ones, but he did play.
What was it? World of Warcraft or no, not that one.
What was the shooting the one where they go to Vegas and everything
called Judy or like fallout or something fallout.
Were they go to Las Vegas?
Yeah, that one.
Grants After Auto. He played that at a friend's house and he's like, I want to go to Vegas.
I want to shoot guns.
You know, he wanted to go and learn how to shoot guns for real.
So it does affect their life. It does influence their life.
Sure.
And what they want to do.
Look, this is all just a bunch of BS.
How was that BS?
You did not fact-check anything that you just said what do you mean? I didn't fact-check look all
He said I want to go shoot people
No, he said he wants to learn how to shoot not people he but he wanted to learn how to shoot a gun
After playing Grand Theft Auto
He said I want to go to Vegas and I want to go to this place and learn how to shoot a gun and it turns out
That was a real place
They do have real places in Vegas where you can go and shoot guns at targets
He didn't want to shoot real people. God. No, but I'm just saying it desensitizes kids
right
Right and and I think that people should know how to shoot guns
I think that if you're in a situation where there's a gun that's on the ground
You should be able to pick it up and either a use it to protect yourself and your loved ones or be
deactivate it and take the rounds out and
And make it so nobody else can shoot you with it. I think people should know how to use guns
So I'm pro gun in that regard
I would say I'm pro-gun. I'm pro-peep.
I'd say I'm pro-choice.
Well, that's abortion. Let's say this goes to abortion, not guns, my friend.
Deactivate. Nobody don't laugh at me. You know what I mean.
Disarm disarms the weapon. Is that what I should say God? I'm not perfect with the terms, but it's okay
It's okay. I mean I got 100% on my firearms test when I went there like you have to take a test to buy this gun
I was like a test nobody told me how to take a test
So I studied the booklet for five minutes got a hundred percent on the test
They gave me a gun a week later and California have to wait a week after you buy it. Oh, wow
You have to come back in a week and then pick it up. Yeah
Here it takes about a year for even the police to have approved a gun for them.
Loser zero, I deactivate you too.
I deactivate you.
Turn off the AI.
No, I'm saying I think it's important for people to know how to use guns.
I do.
Especially to respect guns.
You don't point it at anyone unless you're going to use it.
Unless you're going to pull that trigger, you do not point it at a real person.
You could point it at a target, but you do not point it at a real person unless you're gonna pull that trigger because it could go off
You could have a freaking
Tremor in your finger. You could have a freaking seizure in your finger and shoot someone, you know, just like
There's a lot of back to that actor a lot of extra though. Um, yeah, I'm Jim
Alec Baldwin. Yeah, I'll look Baldwin. Oh my god, like I can't believe he didn't get any kind of
Anything from that they just were like, oh, it was an accident. I'm sorry
Well, I'm sure it wasn't on purpose. I mean if you would have been on purpose you wouldn't be happy
It was an accident. I mean it could sometimes happen. I know. I know it was an accident that happened, but
still you should have gotten some kind of
punishment for I think killing a person in general
Yeah, but it's hard. He's handed it. He's handed a prop, you know, you put trust in your prop department to make sure everything's
Yeah, he did he put that's true and somehow the prop department let live rounds in that weapon like that's not okay
That's not cool at all. And I when I learned how to shoot guns
I had never touched a gun till I was like 34 and then my friends. Yeah, right
No, I'd never shot a gun. My parents are super anti-gun. I'd never even seen a gun in real life
Your parents were pro-life. They're anti-gun
Anti-motorcycle anti-gun. They were just very protective and I couldn't stand it. But anyways, you saw my yeah
They hated motorcycles too
But when I was like around 34, I think it was I was dating this guy. His friend was an ex-army ranger
They took me out and he had all like his guns out in the desert
And so there was everything from like a 22
To a freaking shotgun and he had me shoot every single one and then they just
Tracked which when I was most comfortable with the most accurate with and it was a 45
She's weird for a girl. I know but
Automatic
45 is like one of the bigger ones, so it doesn't fit in a purse easily, but you can still get a big purse
Oh, okay. Okay. Yeah. Yeah, so that's the gun that I bought was an HK 45 USP and
That's what I own
Yeah, it does have kick and that's the thing which was weird is that I was accurate so with that kick
It's almost like I expected the kick and so
It made me more accurate. I'm not sure why it made me more accurate. Oh, I got removed
You're back. So you're back. I didn't take you off. I didn't take you off. You fell off. Yeah, it was my my internet cut out
Okay, you're back. You're back back in black. Do you have good internet in Hong Kong?
I'm not in Hong Kong anymore. I actually got back yesterday. Where are you now or you don't have to tell us? That's fine
Oh, I'll tell you. I'm Oklahoma
Okay, okay. Yeah, nice. Okay. See I know that he you're an okay
He said he was converting people who's giving those personalities tests and in the emeter's
Hong Kong it didn't take to a very well though, right? What is that like Scientology? Yeah, are you a Scientologist?
for $50,000, I was a Scientologist.
There you go.
Yeah, well, exactly.
That's all they care about is the money.
It didn't go into the wheel,
so they shipped us back early.
So I got 50 grand and only had
two months instead of six.
You're gonna pay 50 grand for that.
Because you 50 grand?
Oh, hold on a second.
Yeah, I got 50 grand for that.
Wow, yeah, I need to go to some other countries incredible because they can we do tarot cards there and no
They do they do is hand on personality tests. Yeah, everyone has a special personality turns out. Yeah
Everyone can be helped by Scientology turns out
Nathan test was just a white giant and all the people would come up to me and so it was like
I really didn't have to do anything. I live in Southern California where the Scientologists you choose like you were just they're rampant
They're everywhere. They're trying to convert everyone the Liberty Center, right?
Yeah, there's some damn assholes
All right, but you're not but you're not one I'm just very confused here
You're so you're you were there doing a mission for science policy because $50,000 you didn't say you didn't convert anybody
Yeah, I'll do anything for 50,000. It's not even very much money when it comes down to like, you know money it's like
$50,000, but yeah, I guess we're passing on personality test. It's not bad
Yeah, it was just in Boyle says I heard sick disrespect spunky he has a beatdown coming his way
I agree. It's Justin. Fuck that guy if he said anything disrespectful to my spunky. He's fucking done
I can't believe that that was the happening last night.
Well, it's disrespectful to everybody.
It's because he hates himself so much.
He's so fucked up that he can talk shit on other people.
No, I say don't even let him fucking have a platform
or speak that.
That's bullshit.
She's amazing.
I love Spunky.
He doesn't really have a platform.
He has a rumble now.
And nobody even lets him on anymore, so.
But I still I still humor him
Here it gives him a platform to speak from and that's not sure but it's like, you know
He's talking bullshit. Yeah, but it's like
It's good for people to disagree with people they see too, so they know what they yeah, he's just like he's harmless pretty much
I think he's harmless right his mom. I don't think he's harmless. I mean words can do damage, but obviously she's stronger than that. She doesn't
You know need to be baby
SIG was just talking shit on spunky, and I just thought that was fucked up
He doesn't have any place to speak from he's so
It's frustrating I get it
Yeah, oh
Deactivate you deactivate you loser. I
Love the loser. He's cool
but
Yeah, Rick you still here
Yep, I'm here. I'm just listening
All right, so we lost you for a second man. Nope
What if I didn't cut out yet?
Doesn't usually cut out at like a certain time at night. They just kind of
No, I think that was just a glitch, but it seems to cut out quite a bit
Yeah, in my town we actually have like a hour where everyone has to go off like the internet like they cut the routers
Five milligrams of volume ain't gonna do shit. You need 10 milligrams. That's what I always gave my patients when they were getting um anal
Anal probe for anal ultrasounds. Oh, those are not cool. That's for prostate cancer boys. You can look forward to that
You may have to get the biggest freaking probe I've ever seen stuck up your ass and I made sure to sedate them pretty well
They didn't let me give them enough actually. I think they should have gotten more than 10 milligrams
They got 10 milligrams of volume and
Five I forgot what they got of the what the other med was. Yo psyche. Honestly, it's been so long. Yeah, you ever tried to Tura?
Uh
Solvia, is it Solvia you're talking about? It's for a DT u r a
Yes, I'll be a before okay. I have I don't think I have I don't think I have I have out of a bong
So I had to be a bong. I thought it was weed. I smoked it like weed. I was fucking lit
Yeah, for about a minute
nice
I dreamed that I
What you smoked salvia and you thought it was weed
Well, they just handed me a bong and I thought it was gonna be weed
So I smoked it like a bong of weed so I took a big fat hit. I didn't know that it was salvia in there
So it was a bong, you know, I thought we were smoking weed and so when I after I smoked it
I was like, oh shit and my head just kind of knotted down a little bit
And I had this whole dream that I was riding on a white horse and I was listening to Neil Young and
That was about it for about a minute and then I woke up and I was like, okay moving on
It was fun. It was fine
I just didn't know what I was getting into I was up in Portland at a friend's house and where I lived
We didn't have people smoking salvia out of bongs
I've never look it out of a bong I've never done drugs before
Okay, that's cool
Why are you asking about salvia then with the proper name? Yeah, why are you why are you asking that?
I never asked about salvia
Oh, that was psyche I
Didn't know it's almost into the tour and I thought I was salvia detour
Yeah
What is salvia?
It's the tour. It's the same thing. It's the plant. Yeah, you fucking high for a few seconds
They're out of your mind on it and like I see if you don't just go to people do smoking salvia on YouTube
They just go they go nuts, right?
I've never seen anybody go nuts. I just see him they get a little bit like out of it like DMT
I seen some got member. Oh psyche. Remember that guy uncle Jack that came on your panel
Yeah, he got totally decimated up here
No, we did I don't think he was I mean was that bad?
But yeah, I've seen him smoke DMT before and he just kind of like nods out
But in his mind, he's probably having like a whole trip that none of us know about
Yeah, I don't like that shit. That's really strong that only lasts for 30 minutes or 30 second
I'm sorry, not 30 minutes. Salvi only lasts for like a minute. I think it felt like 30 minutes though
Felt like a really long trip
DMT is really quick too. It's like a really yeah, but it feels like long. I've never done DMT, but it feels like longer, huh?
Oh, wow, it is intense like I spoke to a bunch of times with a pen recently
They have like you know the big pen that they had a big pen with the DMT and they can make that wow
It's so strong. Yeah, that's what uncle Jack had the one time I watched on his channel and he had like
He got naked and stuff. We're like, oh my gosh
But his dick was below the normal the camera level, you know, so it was like
But you did not that does not happen to you. Thank goodness, but how but when you do it how long does it feel like it's long last longer than
No, it let me let's use an MAO I inhibitor which they just what they do in like, you know, the shamanic ones
They have a look and so that this is so that that's why they you know the trip on
The DMT trips down there last a lot longer. They last for hours actually it's like
Yeah, because it only lasts for a few minutes if you smoke at the right regular though here like we do here
Do an MAOI inhibitor last longer? Yeah, much longer. Yep
Biscuit what yeah a Chinese biscuit. It's a type of drug or what about like a Chinese trisket? I
Don't think so
Well, I ate a bunch of mushrooms and acid when I was in high school and stuff, but that was like not
I like the I like shrooms cuz they make me laugh
They sort of would upset my stomach a little bit, but I heard that if you make him a tea it affects your stomach less
What about what about peyote?
Never tried it. Have you?
No, I heard it's really bad
Don't know that's that's more like you got to go to an Indian Reservation getting good with the leaders of that tribe and
Yeah
Being like a sweat lodge and shit like I'm not I don't have that access
Beedah says let's do cadnip
Where are you?
Hi, Beedah. You're psyche. He always jumps out. He'll come back
Psychic come back
So what are you guys all about do you have your own channels do you do your own shows or are you just on this panel for fun or what?
I just find psyche I
Just looking for some people to talk to you
yeah you just wanted to chat I'm a long time fan awesome do you have anything
like specific that you want to chat about miss you to be the love you girl
Rick muted himself yeah really my bed I was coughing
Do you have a specific topic that you want to discuss or anything specific that you want to
Tell us about yourself or what you're going through are you going through something do you need to vent?
You don't want to hear it
Try me
I'm a good listener try me
Well
Nah, I can't I can't I can't I can't
Okay, that's fine, too
mind if I say something you
man I
Would I would like to say I have some problems with girls like
I'm fifty-two. I don't really get any ladies anymore
Most of them call me expired grandpa. I just like
As a as a nice lady what
What do you look for in a guy? Hey, what tips do you have?
Yeah, I look for a man that could come up and just say hey, how are you? What's your name?
Like to talk to you like let's get I want to get to know you
Or I would like to take you out like someone's just just honest. Don't play games. Don't do pickup lines
None of that bullshit. We're too old for that shit, you know
I'm gonna be
Older and I don't go for that though
How old are you? I'm 14. No, you're not shut up
How old are you really? Okay, I guess I'm
Apparently these gen X wait, what are the younger kids the gen gen now Gen Z Gen alpha
Apparently, they're different. I can't speak for those chicks, but for older ladies
Because I am one. I'm like older
Apparently
We don't need the games. We don't need the tricks. We don't need the funny lines
We just want someone to be like just just plain and simple. I like you. Let's talk
Yeah, I'd like to talk to you more
Make it maybe less. Maybe I'm being awkward. I don't know fuck. I
Just like the honesty
Now I'm scared I did that to one lady and she go she said you get away. I'm 19
Well, you were picking some chick that was too young for you. She looked older
Well, she must have bad genetics or she smokes too much or something, but just pick better ladies, okay?
Get your picker fixed. You know what Rick? Don't listen to her man. Just just keep doing what you're doing. No
Don't go for these 19 year olds. That's a bad idea. They're not maybe I'll start going to the bingo hall
Maybe we'll be there. Yeah, go pick up out some 80 year olds. There you go. Rick. Do you ever go to the club?
Okay, see they got some clubs. Yeah. Yeah, you can probably a 52 year old can hit on 40 year olds not 19 year old
So Christine. No, no, what is your problem with him trying to find true love?
nothing
So what he hits on like a night. I just think the 19 year old is gonna freak out like she did
He just said she said ill gross cuz he's old. She doesn't want to date her grandpa
For a 52 year old could be her grandfather. Maybe there's a 19 year olds that like older men
Yeah, not common
Not really common and if they do that means they like their grandpa's age, dude. It's like no
Hit on a 35 to 45 year old woman or even 55 go above your age
Maybe she's 65, but maybe you're in love with her, but a 19 year old is gonna just chew you away
How old are you?
I'm 47. I'll be 48 in a couple weeks.
Are you single?
I'm not dating.
Oh.
Rejection again.
No, I'm not rejecting you. I'm just not dating anyone.
I don't want to date anybody. I just give up on men.
Hey, maybe I could turn that around for you.
Give me a chance. I don't think so with your fake voice that you're using. I don't think so
Okay, I guess it's a fake voice. I can tell you're faking it. It sounds real to me. He's faking it
No, no, hi less. I like less Claypool
Are you the people's podcast muted better? What's up less?
We can't hear you are you there
Hello less
What up, man?
Hey less. There's chillin. I'm not chillin
I thought I need I can at first. I wasn't hearing y'all. I had to fix something up to me to hear y'all talk
Sorry about that here a echo. What are you talking into your phone or something? Yeah, I'm talking on my phone. Okay
Are you out of the house? How about Rick should start seeing more like 19? Yeah, it's still echo or no
No, I don't hear it now. I call
Yeah, I hear an echo I
Think something must be wrong with your system then
It's the iPhone
Bita get up here beat those kiddies BKG get up here Bita. I need to talk to my Bita. I miss you girl
Psyche must have gone to eat something. Yeah, who's some new york? Who's some new york?
Not me. I'm the opposite coast
Callie born and bred
Oh, why I've been to New York a couple times though, and I've
Spent a lot of time in New York. I love it there. That's cool
I love New Yorkers. They're less great. You're from the people's podcast
Yeah, why? Yeah, why did they ban me over there? I don't know
You have to talk to the host about it
Yeah, tell us why did they ban you I?
Have no control on that
You're not a mod over there or anything like that
You can pull through
What's up with the people's podcast? I've never been there. I've never seen it
It's just like this but different like what kind of topics do they discuss?
They took a lot of things, you know about police and all that stuff
Okay, that's a different topic different or different or different topics about governments and all that stuff and then sometimes we have arguments
Yeah
That happens here too
Yeah, I know I've been to an on psyches panel when they have arguments and I stay quiet or sometimes I join in
for fun
Hey, your sister on her period. What up J1?
It's your lips
So long my sister. Yo, you still riding your J1. You still riding your bike. I
Haven't done it yet. I'm too lazy screen. Oh, no, that was turn. Hey, I'm sorry. I have to get off my my sister
She's found out she's pregnant. Oh
She'll have a nice baby. I'm sure it'll be fine
You change electoral baby babies are awesome. I love babies
Hey, let me put up the video that I put up. Yo, what's up?
Do you cut any tips about getting girls?
Yeah
Yeah, why is this on you how much I did on my show, uh
Not sure. Okay. We get me up with somebody who's just coming here to sit. No, just me and sitting
Okay, you're not gonna get what I'm saying because you haven't seen them yet.
Do you have hair? Step out of the vehicle?
This is what we were working with.
I have a...
Oh, dear.
Cops like, yep, been there.
Let's cough.
Whoopsies.
Sure.
Aww.
it happens thank god for the blur so how much you had to drink tonight i'm not sure you're not
sure about a lot right probably it's a cop and a man and a lady outfit
step blue tenant what are you doing
all he's missing is like i have a blue thing in the back here oh
You have a tax number, you have money on hand, you have money on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit card, on a credit
We're contact glasses
Recently got glasses, okay the greatest glasses commercial ever if this was all just
You can buy them down at the glass mart open five to seven
What an ad wizard
Okay, don't talk to me
See ya, then
That was a fun night
That was a real fun night
They cops let him go and then he drove again, and they busted him again
That happened to me a couple times
He cops let you go on a fucking DUI and not no DOI
Not a DOI, but the cops pulled me over and told me I can't drive and they told me to park my car
I parked the car
And then when I left, I came back to my car and I took off.
You got pulled over again?
Nah, I didn't get pulled over again.
Oh, I'm glad you didn't get pulled over again.
The cops already know me where I used to live at.
The cops knew me up there, you know what I mean?
They didn't really fuck with me, but some of them didn't like me,
and they just pulled me over.
Yeah.
You had a lot of interactions with the police?
Yeah, cause I filmed them in PA.
Okay in Pennsylvania mm-hmm, okay, my friend lives there
rat-rat
Philly
Atown
Lancaster Habersburg. I don't know the exact town
Oh, but I've never been there. I'd like to go I'd like to go to Chicago too. I've never been there
That's cool. Chi town
I've never been a lot of places in the US. I've been to Hawaii, Oregon, Washington, Washington, D.C., New York, Georgia, Texas, Arizona, Nevada, New Mexico, Colorado.
I've been to Arizona, Casa Grande.
Uh-huh.
Uh-huh. I've been everywhere in Florida. I'll travel. I'll travel a lot. Oh, yeah, I've been to Florida
I went I drove I flew into Florida and then drove got rented a car and drove all the way down the keys
That was such a beautiful trip. Oh worth it. That's fun. I want to take a good road trip do it
Yeah, I did that already
Yes, I love you. I said I would freakin for you that that guy last night was being a total dumb ass
What was that I just heard part of it
Sigg was being a total jerk. She's funky. I think and I think that's wrong. I love her. She's awesome
She's amazing she gets all the love
Yeah, I don't know that much
No, I don't know that much people on on on on psychic panel
I know like a couple people who go to the other panel I go to
Yeah, well sig is one that you should not know because he's just a dick
He's so insecure about himself that he tries to talk bad about other people like he should just stay off the internet really
Oh, wow
He should stay off the internet just like a harry done until he can fix himself
Yeah
Wow, that's crazy. So you record people you do like what's it called first amendment, right videos?
Nah, I just know walk around. I'll just be caught and where where I look why I used to live at the cost in mind
Okay
See in New York to cross get mad. Oh why you be calling me? Uh-uh. That's that's real ridiculous. It's down here in New York
You can't go to a courthouse and in a public place to record because that's how you can't go in with a camera
But that is the law that you can do it
No, it's not a law
You can't go in and in a courthouse and record but you can't go to the
Not in a courthouse not not in the courtroom, but in a public area in the courthouse you can't record
Yeah in the public area you can't yeah
None in the courtroom now. Yeah
But you had people say that you couldn't record in the regular courthouse?
Yeah, like in the public area. They told me you can't record.
They told me not to come in with the camera.
So you said what? Arrest me? Show me that law because it's a law that I can record in the public space?
Nah, I just left it alone. I just left it alone. Just PA in New York is two different laws.
And in Cali, like I've seen people record the courthouse inside the courthouse, but not in the courtroom
Actually, she did take her phone in her purse still recording into the courtroom and recorded some of it
Which was but then that same chick also called a bomb threat into the courthouse. So
Well, that's great
Yeah, that's Daisy. She got arrested by the feds for that. Wow
Yeah, I'll try I'll try to get something like like you have like the little the little on character you have
Not a girl carry a girl, but like a guy character
Yeah, you can make guys too
It's the program's called anima's yes, I so I just think it's more interesting than having a circle on screen anima's
An I am a Zee. Yes. It's alright. It's um, I think it's fun. I think it's better than
I've been doing it for like a year and we do shows with our characters and I can dance. I'm a good dancer
You want to see me dance?
Segi already saw you dancing when psyche was playing the music. Oh shit. Oh, you did I
Can yeah when you were dancing for psyche psyche song get something like that
Wait, DJ, that's what you're doing right now?
Yeah.
Why, were you so?
No, she's dancing right now.
I mean, I mean, not the, ah, how do you say it?
That's actually you, like your movements?
Yeah.
Or your program and it?
Honestly, this is just, I push a button and it does this.
Oh
I mean I could do this dance, but
The guy I think that got other things like on my computer
Like they is a camera that you do the dance and the arm those moji people dance like the one she's doing right now
Yeah, I was thinking I don't I could turn the
It's I forget what it's called, but there is one that'll record your whole body
Yeah, I thought you had that kind of I can do that
This one's a lot easier like I can do Gangnam style. See
What the fuck look at that big-ass fucking rat there
Excuse my language. What did you say?
It's a saw I saw a rat. I saw a big rat came out of the arm the grass and I see one
a rat
New York City I
Guess they have a lot of rats in New York. I don't know we don't have a rat in my yard one time and I put out
it's baking soda and
It's kills the rat. Sorry. I'm not
Nice to these rats that are fucking running trying to run my yard take over my garage, you know
So it's like baking soda and some brown sugar. I think or powdered sugar. I forget
But you put it out in a little bowl and when they eat it they explode apparently I never found an exploded one though
But the rats never came back to my yard
So oh
It worked
Cartoon is creepy. Oh you think cartoons are creepy. You're scared of the little cartoons BSBB. Oh
Well, you should you know probably turn off the TV then it's time for your bedtime
If you're scared of the cartoons, you know
You know
But J1 what are you all about?
Look at my blank my brain just went blank. I don't know. How you doing? It's my first time me DJ
Electric, how you doing your first time here?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Sure, you're sure you're from California. I'm from New York. Go hard on it. No hard on New York
We're part of California. You're from what I said too much information. That's fine. I it's known online. I'm from the LA area
Los Angeles
I was born and raised here
I'm an Anaheim Angels fan
The Los Angeles Angels I guess now
Yeah, I'll confuse. Why do you call it the Anaheim? Why not call it LA Angels? Why do you change it to Anaheim?
Anaheim is not in Los Angeles, actually. It's in Orange County, and that was what they were called from day one.
Anaheim Angels, and then they changed it to the Los Angeles Angels. I don't know why.
Stupid.
But we're not actually in LA. We're in the county south.
Well, I hear Irish County. I think of very very Republican area and high-income area, right?
Yeah, not all of us though, but it's known for that. Sure. Okay. It's like the only Republican County in
California
Yeah, because the Democrats every two years
They'll they'll always you know, they spend a lot of money in that Irish County ever trying to win seats
But then I haven't been successful
No
Cool, so you must be a huge crowd fan right trout the centerfielder. Well, I don't know if I remember trout. Sure. Mm-hmm
Add up my angels and a high ducks, right?
Yeah, I saw the ducks play in the playoffs once. Yeah, that was fun
cool, cool, cool
Yeah, I mean, I'm a huge Yankee fan
but
Yeah, when you bring what I hear
But I did there was a time in the 90s that the angels always used to beat the Yankees
That was one team that you know during the Yankees dynasty
I was one to you that I couldn't beat in the regular season the angels
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I don't know why but never did I think it's the same ballpark, right?
Yeah, it's the same ballpark. The big A. That's what they call it, right? The big A in Anaheim.
Yeah, there's a big A out front. Mm-hmm. Yeah, cool. I've been going there since I was a little kid.
Yeah, how you like the new... Well, it's not... It's the same stadium, but they renovated it.
You like it now or back then? I haven't been recently, so I wouldn't know.
Yeah, I take my son all the time and then when he got old enough to go on his own like he's like mom
He don't need to come. I wish to go to a baseball game again
They have a new train station right there so you can take the train from wherever and just pull in right to the angel stadium pretty much
How far is LA LA to come on about an hour drive
But with traffic you can take up to two hours three three even
Okay, because old Tony's to play on that with the angels remember old Tony the Japanese
Angels yes, we're like six seven years
Okay, well, who was the other one that played for in Seattle. Oh
Each year each year
Uh, how's your summer so far? It's hot here. It's fucking hot right now
And I don't have my AC on because I'm on on this panel. So like my oh, otherwise it's too loud
I mean, you're too. Yeah, it's disgustingly hot
It's like yeah, it's burning high in New York
My best friend lives in New York
Earlier today
What part of New York do you all live in I live in a little Manhattan temporarily?
Yeah, I live in Harlem uptown
Okay, nice
Yeah, I've been my friend lived right across from ground zero for a while right there on the Hudson and a big high-rise
apartment building I went there before
9-11 happened and then I went after 9-11 and it was just like so different then she moved to
What's across the bay that fancy freakin she was investment banker oh
She got real rich now
She lives in some bougie part of New York with like a country club, and I'm like I don't know
I don't really have much in common with you anymore. You're still my best friend. I love you, but I don't go to no country clubs
She's not in the city anymore, she's up she's up more like by Long Island like
Oh, I see a lot. Oh, what do you call that place?
She live around where Bruno lives, that's you.
Yeah, what do you call that place?
It happens.
Something like that, yeah.
She still commutes to, into the city.
But, yeah.
I haven't seen her in a new house.
She probably takes the long island bus.
We call that the hub.
No, she'll take the train from where she's at.
Okay, okay.
All right, I don't know she she just got she's too smart about money. She's really good with money. I am not good with money
Training with money like I'll spend I'm good at spending it
Yeah
Put the money in the side just look at about it and then when the next time you need the money
You just try to remember where you put it at
That's the problem. I'll forget where I put it at bro. I'll but forget
I'll be like oh, I hit it somewhere and now I hit it so good
That's like my vibrator hit my vibrator from myself so good. I can't find it now now. I'm worried if I die
Someone's gonna find it when I die. Oh, I need to find it to hide it better. It's all the way
You know, it's like the episode meets us
when I put money away and then maybe a couple of months later,
I was fighting and I said, oh, wow.
Yo, Lil Nas, yo, JN, yo, J1, right?
I hit some weed up, right?
I hit it somewhere and I forgot all about it, right?
And then when I didn't have no more weed,
I said, yo, what I weed, what I put it at?
And the day I was moving out,
yeah, the day I was moving out, I found that shit.
Where was it hidden? What was your great hiding?
It was in my suitcase where all my clothes was when I was packing up
Wow
Yeah, these guys were like vibrator is still in there like right now. It's not inside me gaudy
I know that for sure. I checked there those first place to check duh. That's too much info
Mmm, it's not in there and loser says lecture. Thank you for being honest. Yeah, of course
It's hidden somewhere in my closet. I can't find two of them actually and you in your 40s
Jump Wow
I had a son at home and then when he grew up and moved out
Then I got vibrators, but when he lived here, I was like no, I'm not having anything like that
You know, okay, he could find it. So but when
Yeah, I mean how many kids you have have your money action one
He's grown now. He's don't have don't have no more kids
I mean, I would have but I never got married. So I didn't like that. I got three kids
Oh, you got three. I didn't know that look. Yeah, I got two girls and one boy the one I told you
When I was talking about I had I had to go to court and and fight custody from
Yeah, you told me that yeah, I finally got the custody you know I mean
That's the only reason why I'm down in New York for now
But I'm out of here in a couple weeks stay by your kids as much as you can
Yes, ma'am. I think that's important like
When I graduated nursing school in 2003 and then I moved to get a job for nursing his dad stayed where he was
And he didn't want to move with us, which was fine. We weren't together. I get it
but I think that was
Not beneficial for my son and I do feel bad about that
Yeah, but there were the nursing jobs up there. We're not good enough like they just weren't good
What I said, New York no in Northern, California. Oh
Like we were living kind of in the boonies of NorCal in Humboldt, if you know where that is.
I think so.
No, Oakland is like by San Fran, and if you drive five hours north, you're still in California, but you're in Humboldt.
That's where they grew all the weed.
Yeah.
Back in the day before it was legal, yeah.
It's a cool place to live. It's beautiful. The redwood forests are gorgeous. It's right on the beach, too.
I've seen it snow on the beach there.
Like it's just such a weird crazy place. It's beautiful, but
There's just not a lot of diversity and there I wanted my son to grow up with it more diversity more culture more art more everything and
I saw up there, and I was like well he can grow up with a bunch of rednecks and
That's just not
Humboldt University is still there. That's where I went to nursing school
Humboldt State University
Oh your nurse just like Christine mm-hmm all right yeah I've been a nurse for 20
years wow oh I'm retired now because of an injury but that is neither here nor
there
Now I do YouTube shows and make crazy videos like weird random shit like oh here
Let's play this one. Oh, what's the name of your YouTube channels? I could check your videos
DJ Electra Fry
DJ Electra. Yeah, I think I saw your stuff on YouTube
Did you? Yeah, I think so. Nice. That's cool
But I didn't know that I was your are you at first, you know me
Yeah, DJ I looked a fry and
DJ is in a wheelchair gotty like you for real. No, I'm not in a wheelchair. No, it's nothing like that
Justin Boyle nothing like that psyche put up my video, please. Oh
I can drop my link I can put it in chat even
A word?
A word.
So I make silly videos like that. No
J1 that day that day on psyche was playing music
He was playing music that I didn't hear no music when when I hopped in the pan
Remember
Like you was you like you was on the on panel when I went in and and I say yo, what up J1 and you didn't answer me and
And they said
He was yes. Yes. Oh, I didn't know I didn't know that cuz I didn't hear the music when I got on
I just need here. I just heard one person talking and they stopped talking. I mean hit the music at all
Yeah, but I forgot what music he was playing
Hey guys guys, I just want to thank thank you spunky like I just take that side. I got a little packages
You're like, monkey, thank you so much.
Aw.
Ta-la-la?
That's me.
It was a box in a bag?
Yeah, box in the bag, OK?
OK, I'm not being good for the planet, but that's OK.
Oh, hey.
You want Amazon, do better.
This is awesome, OK.
Oh, shit.
Look at this, OK.
These are perfect.
That's a looser.
Oh, there's your dishes for your kiddies. Yes, nice elevated cap. Those are so nice.
They're beautiful. Thank you. I'm going to put them up right now. Those are beautiful.
Oh, yeah. Who's that? Okay. This is from Spunky. Thank you so much, Spunky. I'll be right
I'm going to fill these up real quick. What else did you get? Okay, I'll get that right
Those are really nice spunky. Well done
What's the first yes, you know, she has kiddies too, right? I think I've seen her appear with kiddies or was that
Oh, oh my gosh, no my gosh, I think I know
my god
They see me see it. I have to put extra. Oh my god. That's a big box. Yeah. Oh my god
What is it? What could it be?
Give us a hint.
It's a sex one.
A hint is, hint is neon.
Neon, oh shit, oh shit.
Yeah, oh fuck.
Oh my god, okay.
Hold on, this is so cool.
Let's take it. Okay. Okay. Okay. Yes always wash everything first for sure
My friend I sent my clothes Casey
I sent him new sheets because he said his sheets were worn out because he humped his bed too much
So I sent him new sheets for his birthday yesterday, and he was just gonna put him on his bed
I'm like no you gotta wash them
Don't sleep on these sheets from some random factory that you don't even know where it came from
I don't know
Wash the shit first. Yeah, I guess you're gonna watch. Oh, yeah. Oh shit. It's so cool. Huh? Okay?
Hey, look here a little like that cuz it's so cool. I'll show you
Over here. Come on get over there
Oh, it's a light up. What is it?
It's hard to see it. It's bright. It's bright. I'll throw up the light one. Can you turn it off a different like to more brightness?
Hold on
It's a way to
This is pretty bright, but it looks I mean it looks perfect here. It's just kind of bright on the screen. It's a
other light out in your house
Yeah, I just don't know all the lights out so bright. Oh, wow. It's an alien. Oh
Alien only a cat. Oh an alien with a cat. How cute. I love it. Oh
My god, I love it. It looks so good
It's like this doesn't do justice on this on this on the computer screen, but it looks so good
Oh my god, it looks so good. I love it
Have it look good so you can show it on the computer
But maybe put it in the window in the window sill where it's really I'll show you I'll show you a picture from uh
It's from the page the page. Let me see. I love it. It is I love it. Thank you so much. It's monkey. They're awesome
I mean cats and I
Love them. Thank you so much
On Amazon shit. Okay. Yeah, I just I just put that on cuz I just thought that I was like, I love that
But it has different settings where you can turn it down to a lighter setting my I'll have a look
Yeah, Amazon
Okay, so my list, okay, this is so cool, okay, list, right here.
Hi, Sweet Pea.
That's what I used to call my son when he was a baby.
I called him Pumpkin Head and Sweet Pea.
Okay, here's what it looks like.
Ooh, okay, okay, this is what it looks like.
Oh, it is like so beautiful. It's such a beautiful color. It's so cute. Yeah, I'm sure there's a way to set it so you can see it on live
Okay, I'll have a look at it. Oh, look at it. Thank you so much. Bunky. Love it
I'm gonna put some and wash the bowls and put them in the back of the road quick one second. Oops
Just fix this. Okay. Go back
Okay
Pumpkin had a good movie never see the head movie. I just called my son that cuz he had a really big head
He would like to fall over when he was learning to walk because his head was so big you just be like
Okay, it was a crazy movie. They like there's like some like weird weird person in the town
I think they all kill him on Halloween or something. He comes back as
I'm not gonna scary movies, but I watch a ton of true crime and so I'm like, I don't really understand that whole dynamic
Why I can't handle scary movies, but I can handle true crime. It makes no sense
I know because like movies are like I was like they were the one scared movies because they were they were so fake like it was kind of like
It's kind of like obviously they were laughable. I should have realized that as a kid, but I didn't realize that they were laughable
Now I can laugh at them I guess
Yeah, I used to like I thought it's like they my own suit. I was like six years old. I was like my favorite
Wendy's favorite, too. Isn't that right? Yeah, Freddie. Yeah, and that's when he's favorite. She was Chuck E. T.
Huh?
Yeah
The guy that played
Robert England. Yeah, and she met him
Howard sent her with one of the interns or the one of the staff
Fucking remember his name right now, but
They went up in Florida, Robert England was there, and they met, they met him, yeah, I got cool to interview her about that. That was really cool.
Yeah, I think I don't think her handlers liked me very much, so I'm, but...
No, those guys were total dicks, and you know they all...
Kind of had a falling out now. Oh, yeah. Yeah, and now she's kind of on her own again
Oh, no, so if you can go up there and you know, yeah
I'm not I'd love her about being a fan, but just talk to her about real life. Yeah
Let's you up. Yeah. Okay
She just doesn't like a lot of times. She doesn't like doing questions. She doesn't want to be a question. I got you
I got you. What was your favorite thing about talking to Howard or anything like that? She just doesn't like that
She just wants to talk about regular everyday stuff
Yeah, what is hard? I mean it's kind of it is hard to like you know with doing an interview and stuff like that
It's hard to
No, exactly here. What's it talk about? I mean, I know that she loves McDonald's and homie a couple of guests
Hold on a second. Yeah. Oh, yeah, so, you know, it's a she's a horror movie. They learned that about her
So she loves horror movies. So watch them on her channel on rumble too. She loves them
What are you guys doing over here?
Hello
Is it easy
Oh
That is his name is ravioli. I don't know. Yeah, you can call me ravi. Oh, hey, Ravi. How are you? Is that your picture?
Nice looking man. Thank you. It's older man. I like it
Jay, how you doing psyche? How you do it? I guess you was picking up the packages when I first
Yeah, X. Hello. Oh, yes, what up?
Thank you. Thank you for being you. Hope you enjoy your gifts. What's bucky? Thank you for the
I'm well, how are you?
But I did a show and had a few shots and I feel a little bit better. I love your posters
This is my two favorite bands of all time to a limping Floyd me too
Well, she's in the sauce
That's so cool. I love it. Oh, is that cocaine?
What okay? Oh, who is it? Oh, it's it's fucking Canada dry. Oh you
No, my name is Ravi
Ready!
Alright, here we go!
This is Wendy's intro that I made for her
Wendy from Howard Street
Wendy, Wendy, she's so fine
Wendy, Wendy, where she gonna die?
It's Ravi
Bobby and the Donalds
This Wendy needs a break to the day
Oh, come on, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that
This Wendy fuck
She's a virgin
What the fuck my name is corned if I love to dance wait wait, I'm paying out with Wendy
Well good for her I guess oh
Yeah, she really wants to fuck like she has a list of like 20 guys that she wants to bang
But she's a virgin
I know some guy named Gregory. He's a virgin still and he's that I just want to look for a wife
And he's a good guy though, but
No, yeah, she'll be anybody if she got the chance. She just hasn't got the chance
There's not women many women out there that want to fuck that are still virgins, you know, that says something
Okay.
Wendy, Wendy, she's so fine.
That's 2G.
Wendy, Wendy, where she's going to die, probably at McDonald's.
Because Wendy needs her break today.
Wendy had her break today.
So she wrote what all these guys should say for her.
She wrote and emailed them and said, call my show and say this.
What do you want me to say here?
I'm reading it right now, Wendy.
Okay.
Wendy is awesome she wrote that hold on let me make sure I get this all right
okay I think I got this I love giving out orange juice and hanging up with my
favorite friend Wendy she wrote that let me try another take I love giving out
orange juice and hanging with my awesome friend Wendy girl
That's the most pressure I've been in in a long time.
That's OJ.
OJ is funny.
I love her laugh.
That was fun.
Hey, my name is Sexy's Potato,
and I love my Sexy's Hot Wife Wendy.
What tube?
This for new or my new intro I need dance in.
hit, come in, and do it on my live stream.
She didn't need you to say all that, stupid.
Three, two, one.
Hey, my name is Sexy's Potato,
and I love my Sexy's Hot Wife, Wendy.
On to this-
She said she married him.
On to the intro.
I knew it.
Now we miss the potato?
I think it's supposed to stop at Wendy's-
That's Cardiff Electric.
On my live stream, what?
Hey, my name is Sexy's Potato, and I love my Sexy's Hot, no, Wendy!
Hey, my name is Sexy's Potato, and I love my Sexy's Hot Wife, Wendy.
Smile and dance, monkey!
Hey, my name is Tukie and I love hanging out with my baby doll Wendy. Wow
Okay, you want me to do it again just just in case
My name is Tukie and I love hanging out with my baby doll Wendy
Hacker Hacker
Didn't say one. No, he's got a really popular. So you don't have to say one
Did you ever see Wayne's world? I don't watch shows like this. Yeah, you don't say one. All right in three two one
Hey, my name's sexy's potato and I love my sexes hot wife Wendy
Jesus it cut print we got it wrote to say that in the dance Wendy on YouTube
That's her friend, uh, forget her name.
Alright, where's the thirsty motherfucker's this?
We're gonna fuck anything.
Wimby needs you.
Look at that face look at that face when they need you you thirsty motherfuckers Wendy and her favorite food is spaghetti and meatballs
Spaghetti and meatballs
I have a new light lease on life, I love pink sauce wait wait wait wait remember that lady that was selling the pink sauce
I heard she's going to blue now
So good
It's like marinara mixed with cream sauce kind of I guess. I don't really know. I never made it
Vodka actually. Oh, I don't like vodka sauce at all. No
It's too sweet on my pot. You like raviolis. I
do I'm more of a fan of that a
Ragu or a what about pesto? I don't
Love pesto as it does go well on ravioli, but I'm more into like
cheeses and meats and tomatoes and italiano
Is the pesto the green one? Yeah, that's a green. Oh, yeah, that's a good one. That's a good one
There's a red
Fucking good one made out of basil. Oh my neighbor grows the own basil right in my yard
And then comes and picks it because I said you could grow a basil in my yard. Sure
The green shit is good though pesto so good
So I like a penny
Penny is a rigger don't a penny affect the Cheney
Cappellini
Gotta hit a little bit of the accent
Little ZD sound very good. I'm like boxes a ZD
Yeah, you can get it in a box ZD
Mm-hmm. You have a little box is ZD big ZD box. So big ZD. It's good stuff
You ever seen this the brand I was there
Never really watched it. I wasn't here at that time. I think I was watching on the wire before I was watching soprano
Yeah, I like the wire better
Was the chat say
Easy looks like he's straight out of 1993
The same by the bell guy
Screech. Yeah
I got caught that many times like a Puerto Rican screech. Yeah. Yeah, you're the Puerto Rican screech
Beedah's back. Get up here, Beedah. Get your little skinny butt up here, Beedah.
I will kick it.
Oh, kick it. Yes, you can. Can you kick it? Yes, you can.
Okay, sorry.
Can you kick it? Yes, you can.
I got you. I got you and beta are my favorite and Jamie's kitties and
Jamie Jamie beta he man
Damn, I forgot me the girls that never turn their backs on
Yeah, yeah, those those those and shout out to sponky. Oh, um, that little Amazon gift
What happened to Tina
Who I call her Jamie's kiddies. I know she's Jamie's Cowboys, but I call her Jamie's kiddies
She was an old biker. Oh
You look like a man, but was a woman. I loved her X was her name, right?
I hope I still alive. Yeah, she's not alive. She'd be on other people's families now. I seen that round
Oh, she's alive and she just doesn't come here one of these days that throat's gonna give away
Don't like that. She's fucking so cool. Like I wish she was my mother like she's my life education
I would have gotten if she was a man